https://cepp.com/privacy-statement/

HomeAbout What Makes Us Unique About Our StaffExpertise Pretrial Justice Evidence-Based Practices Justice Involved Women Sex Offenders Probation and Parole Reentry Collaboration Justice Reinvestment Strategic Planning Additional Areas of ExpertiseResource CentersClientsNewsContactSusan Gibel Memorial Page
Select PageHomeAbout— What Makes Us Unique— About Our StaffExpertise— Pretrial Justice— Evidence-Based Practices— Justice Involved Women— Sex Offenders— Probation and Parole— Reentry— Collaboration— Justice Reinvestment— Strategic Planning— Additional Areas of ExpertiseResource CentersClientsNewsContactSusan Gibel Memorial Page
Privacy Statement
Home Privacy Statement
Information Use
Cookies
A cookie is a small piece of data stored on a user’s computer and is used to tie a user’s information to a particular Web site. Cookies cannot be run like a program, nor can they be used to deploy viruses to a user’s computer. A cookie can only be accessed by the Web site from which it was created and cannot be used to collect information about a user’s computer or the data on the computer.
The Center Web site makes use of cookies to store session data, registration information, and survey data. The information stored in these cookies is not collected and cannot be viewed by Center staff members or other parties associated with the Center.
Cookies can be disabled by following the instructions in your browser’s help manual. The only drawback of disabling cookies is that the user may experience problems with the functionality of parts of this Web site.
Information Collection
Registration
During registration for a CEPP event, a user is required to provide some personal information including name, email address, and contact information. The Center uses this information to facilitate event coordination. Under no circumstance is the information provided to or shared with third parties.
Links
This Web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of other sites. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.
Contact Information
If users have any questions or suggestions regarding the Center’s privacy policy, please contact Susan Gibel.
About Us The Center is a nonprofit organization first incorporated in Pennsylvania in 1981 with its main office in Kensington, Maryland, and satellite offices throughout the United States. The Center’s staff and network of expert consultants are configured into project teams that have diverse qualifications and backgrounds in corrections, organizational development, nonprofit management, training, criminal justice, human services research, agency administration, and policy development.
Copyright The content available on this Web site, including but not limited to text, graphics, photographs, presentations, documents, scripts, software, and Web applications, are protected by copyright and are the property of the Center for Effective Public Policy.
No part of this Web site may be copied, modified, transmitted, broadcast, or reproduced in any form whatsoever without the prior written permission of the Center for Effective Public Policy.
Quick LinksPrivacy Statement
© Copyright 2020 The Center for Effective Public Policy
